question_data = [
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"medium",
    "category":"Entertainment: Music",
    "question":"Ashley Frangipane performs under the stage name Halsey.",
    "correct_answer":"True",
    "incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Soulja Boy&#039;s &#039;Crank That&#039; won a Grammy for Best Rap Song in 2007.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Pink Guy&#039;s debut album was &quot;Pink Season&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Metallica collaborated with Rowan Atkinson&#039;s Mr Bean on a 1992 comic relief single.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"&quot;The Division Bell&quot; is the final album of the progressive rock band Pink Floyd.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"&quot;Neutral Milk Hotel&quot; is a real band.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"A Facebook campaign placed Rage Against The Machine&#039;s &quot;Killing in the Name Of&quot; as the UK Christmas Number 1 in 2009.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"EDM label Monstercat signs tracks instead of artists.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Green Day&#039;s album &#039;American Idiot&#039; is considered a &quot;punk rock opera.&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]